<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Vihaan Krishna</title><link>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content on Vihaan Krishna</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href="https://github.com/malkarisreenivasulu">Vihaan Krishna&lt;/a> 2021</copyright><atom:link href="http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Evolution of the Sidhartha Gautama Buddha</title><link>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/evolution-of-the-sidhartha-gautama-buddha/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 18:02:58 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/evolution-of-the-sidhartha-gautama-buddha/</guid><description>EVOLUTION OF SIDDHARTHA GAUTAMA BUDDHA This is the story of the greatest Indian sage lived 2500 years ago inspiring millions of people with his great teachings showing a path towards enrichment of life. Today Buddhism is the fourth largest religion in the world, religion of peace and happiness. He was the son of a king a prince who has every luxurious comforts in life. He left a rich life of pleasure and prepared to leave himself to seek ultimate enlightenment.</description></item><item><title>Nourish the Soul Nourish the Life</title><link>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/nourish-the-soul-nourish-the-life/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 17:59:21 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/nourish-the-soul-nourish-the-life/</guid><description>NOURISH THE SOUL, NOURISH THE LIFE When we are little kids we spend all our daydreaming of becoming something great, dreaming of wonderful things going to do, we will tell our friends, the family that we will become a doctor, racer, fighter, or pilot, as a child we believe and dream with endless possibilities. as we are unaware that time as dreaming is also one form of planning. so never stop dreaming and our all plans are always possible.</description></item><item><title>Train Your Money Management Skills</title><link>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/train-your-money-management-skills/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 17:57:44 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/train-your-money-management-skills/</guid><description>TRAIN YOUR MONEY MANAGEMENT SKILLS Personal financial decision-making is so Crucial and so important, money management skills are more than what is being organized. We do have so many bucket strategies for diversifying and reaching the financial goalsEven though we have so many financial planning strategies we still end up with bad investment failures because of a lack of commitment to the strategies and their rules. Investment in stock markets runs between optimism and pessimism, the loss of accession creates the temptation to sell the stock when the markets are so low, and risk tolerance is one of the major psychological factors which affects investments.</description></item><item><title>Are You Recycling Your Plastic Bottles</title><link>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/are-you-recycling-your-plastic-bottles/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 17:48:10 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/are-you-recycling-your-plastic-bottles/</guid><description>ARE YOU RECYCLING YOUR PLASTIC BOTTLES The usage of plastic bottle containers for your drinking water or beverages has become the most economical and cost-efficient strategy in the drinking &amp;amp; package industry. After using it are we disposing of it in the recycle bins? If we are trashing it properly then we are contributing an important part of the product&amp;rsquo;s life cycle and helping the environment as it can be recycled and reused for making something new product again.</description></item><item><title>Creating New Third</title><link>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/creating-new-third/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 11:25:38 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/creating-new-third/</guid><description>This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 10:14:43 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/contact/</guid><description>Hello Readers, Good Morning ! If you wanted to contact me you can walkin to sai nagar, balapur, Hyderabad, INDIA.</description></item><item><title>Creating New Second</title><link>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/creating-new-second/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 08:34:31 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/creating-new-second/</guid><description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 08:32:55 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/about/</guid><description>Hello Readers, Good Morning ! My Name is Vihaan Krishna Malkari, I am a blogger, Investor, Reader, Learner. I like Nature. I like to spend my time with my parents. You can follow me on my social media links above.</description></item><item><title>Creating New Post</title><link>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/creating-new-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://vihaankrishna.github.io/blog/creating-new-post/</guid><description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description></item></channel></rss>